Translation and subtitles by
PEPPER & LALASPAIN
*** SONG LIVES FOR EVER ***
Lucy!
Sweetheart, it's Daddy.
Lucy?
Sweetheart?
Lucy? Lucy, it's Daddy, sweetheart.
Wake up, Lucy, come on!
Lucy! Wake up!
What the hell is this thing?
How can I get this off you?
If you move those, you'll kill her.
You're lying.
Perhaps.
But is that a risk
you're willing to take?
Vietnam.
*Foreign language*
Hey, how you doing?
- Screw you!
- Okay.
It's your lucky day, man.
Usually I don't give second chances.
Here's the question.
Whose territory is this?
I said screw you, pussy boy!
*Unintelligible*
What did you say?
I can't hear you.
Louder!
*Unintelligible*
Whose territory?
Master, Master Trahn's.
That's right.
Master Trahn's territory.
So why don't you go home,
and tell you boss to pack up his villa,
and his whores and get the hell out?
Vietnam is closed for business.
You got that?
Yeah?
*Foreign language*
Oh, yeah, it's done.
Oh, I think they will.
S- S- S-
Sorry.
I- I'm...
I- I- I'm...
My... name... is...
Can't remem...
Remember my name.
Can't remember my name.
I can't remember anything.
*Foreign language*
No need.
I can trust you.
*Foreign language*
It's my last job... for anyone.
What are you gonna do back in China?
It's not like your Army buddies
want you back real soon.
Yeah, well.
There's no more fighting for me.
My wife wants a noodle shop.
Then go with that wife of yours. A cook?
- I can't imagine that.
- No need to imagine that at all.
*Foreign language*
Master Trahn,
you don't need to apologise.
For anything.
I'm for ever in your debt.
Er...
Er... English?
I-need-speak...?
Eng- Engl...?
- Br-British Emb...
- Go! Go! Go!
Emb...!
British Emb...
For God's sakes, lady!
I'm trying to find the British Embassy!
The stutt... the stutter's gone.
The stutter's gone!
Thank you!
Buh... buh... buh...
*Foreign language*
English!
Hey, baby!
Sorry I'm late.
Where were you?
Got a surprise for you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I went to the embassy.
The embassy?
Getting my passport back.
We're going home.
- Don't mess with my head.
- I'm not, I'm not... I promise you.
I'm done.
We get to go home.
Thank you.
I love you.
What?
- It's gonna wash up.
- It's not about the shirt.
This was the last time.
Like the last time?
And like the last "last time?"
Or like the one before that?
But I'm done.
I'm done.
Listen to me. I'm done. Trust me!
Maya, look!
My final payment.
It's gonna help us.
Start over.
I don't need your blood money.
Maya!
I'm done!
We... we can...!
We can go home.
Who are you?
*Foreign language*
S.. Sorry.
English?
*Foreign language*
You got to go!
British Embassy?
*Foreign language*
Connor!
Maya?
Yeah?
You're still in town?
Not for long.
Why?
Well, you better get the hell out, man.
'Cos Pop just heard the Russians
might pay you a visit.
I think they already have.
I thought it was a nightmare but...
- What? What are you talking about?
- Hey, Sonny...
How do you think they
found out where I lived?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe they followed you home?
Yeah, that's probably it.
Go!
He's on the move!
North stairs, North stairs!
All right!
We're on our way!
*Foreign language*
We got him, boss.
Just a few more minutes.
And remember, boys...
Big bonus if you bring him to me alive.
Follow him!
What is going on?
Do you have him?
Working on it.
Drop it!
Drop it or I'll blow your brains out.
Take it easy.
Just take it easy.
On the ground. Now!
Good boy!
Hey, boss?
It's Andrei.
I think I'll take that bonus.
*Foreign language*
So... you are Master Trahn's bloodhound.
I just want some tea... some snacks?
No one said you can talk!
I see you boss has put a big price...
on the heads of my men.
Smart to set up the place, Andrei,
*Foreign language*
Genious.
You are still breathing for one reason,
and one reason only.
I want to make an example of you.
The question is...
How precisely?
Where's my wife?
Your wife?
How the fuck should I know?
You don't know?
If I knew you had a wife,
it would be there.
On your bed...
entertaining my men right now.
Okay.
I believe you.
Because you think you have me.
You have balls.
I'll give you that.
But now...
it's time to teach you a lesson.
Here's the lesson.
You should've shot me
when you had the chance.
How's that for entertaining,
you dumb fuck?
*Foreign language*
I love you, Daddy!
Lucy.
Wow! Good morning, Vietnam!
My... my daught...
Please, I need to talk to the police.
What's he saying?
He needs to talk to the police!
Looks like the police already
talked to you... plenty!
- Give it to me.
- I can't!
- It's evidence!
- It's mine!
Help!
What the hell is going on here?
Morning, doctor!
Just another lovely day on the job!
Who is this?
Extremely violent.
No papers, no memory...
Hey, maybe no girlfriend,
so it could be your lucky day.
A Westerner.
Get him a clean private room.
Compresses every hour to lower
the swelling on his face.
We'll be dealing with
the government people soon enough.
And I don't want any trouble.
I'll see him when he wakes up.
She likes him.
The Russians were telling the truth.
They didn't take Maya,
He thought I was done for.
If anything he'd be bragging about it.
*Foreign language*
That's a good question.
Maybe it was your old Army buddies,
Maybe they don't want you back home.
Weren't you like the most
honest guy in your unit?
That's why you left, right?
So, they probably thought...
"Hey, we got a deal."
You might rat them out.
That doesn't make any sense.
They're not smart,
they're not organized...
Half of them are dead,
the other half in jail.
*Foreign language*
She wouldn't have just left.
Not like that.
*Foreign language*
Thank you, Master Trahn.
Don't worry, it's almost over.
*Foreign language*
I'm sorry but she's the key!
It's her DNA that matches and they
pay well for that database, okay?
*Foreign language*
They gave us 20 million in diamonds.
Twenty million!
*Foreign language*
Well, these are not...!
People that you could just refuse!
*Foreign language*
Just one last trade, okay?
We're gonna deliver the artefact.
And then we're done, okay?
So far you've told t0he police
you have no memory.
It's coming back.
Slowly,
but I still have no idea how
I ended up in  bloody V... V...
Vietnam.
The last thing I can remember clearly,
is coming out of the water,
at V... V... V...
Victory Fountain Park!
Victory Fountain Park.
Sorry. It helps with the...
stutter.
Victory Fountain Park?
Yeah.
And you mentioned
you were trapped there.
What do you mean by that?
I don't even know if I can explain it.
Alright? But one minute
I can see the exit.
I can see it, it was right there,
and then the next moment...
I was lost again.
I was walking around in circles.
There's no way to explain it.
Okay? There is something
re-really m-m-messed up
about that place, it is.
And you told the
police you would help
with these people who
kidnapped your daughter.
Lucy.
The longer I spend away from that place,
the m-m-more I can remember but,
they did something to me in there.
This stutter and...
you know, t-t-the...
ticks and...
M-m-m-my...
M-m-m-my memory!
My memory.
Look.
I know my story sounds
pretty crazy, right?
And obviously I'm...
not in the best of shape at the moment
but you could actually check
for yourself if you want because
my daughter, she went missing
just over two weeks ago
but we made the papers last Friday now.
You probably don't have
the papers here but
I could probably get someone
to fax you the articles if...
I... can I use that phone?
It's all right. I can do it myself.
Okay, look, she went missing
the morning of January 1st,
New Years Day.
Andrew.
I'm going to help you.
Thank you.
I have it.
My final payment.
Oh, wait, wait, you still owe me.
For the woman.
No, not diamonds.
You know what I need.
Our business is concluded.
Thank you!
Hey!
Where's my wife?
I'm not gonna ask again.
Sonny, you tell this
asshole I'm serious.
Holy shit!
Wait, wait, wait!
Where do you think you're going?
There you are.
Aliens. Of course.
What the fuck, man?
Let me go.
Where's my wife?
You fucking moron.
You're already dead.
When my father gets here, he's...
Your father's next.
I heard everything.
You wouldn't dare!
That was your rib.
- I'm gonna keep going...
- No, no, no, no!
No, no!
You don't understand, man!
You saw what they could do.
It's not like we had a choice!
You could have warned me.
But you wanted your diamonds.
And your new arm.
No, no, you don't understand, man.
I saw them, I...
I... saw them... eat...
Quan, my cousin.
Remember how we told everyone
it was the Russians that got him?
It wasn't the Russians!
It was the...
These things!
He tried to screw them over
and they tore him...
apart from limb to limb.
And ate him like it was chicken.
Who? What are they?
Aliens? Monsters?
I don't know, man.
They're not from around here.
And I don't mean Vietnam.
No, what you doing?
I'm just gonna cut your arm off.
Maybe you'll take me seriously.
No, no, no, no, no...!
- Where's my wife?!
- I don't know, I don't know...
I don't know.
She's got something on the list.
What list?
Some database. They want people
with specific genetic codes.
What codes?
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
They just wanted people
with a specific DNA sequence.
Your wife just matched.
It was just unlucky, okay?
It was just unlucky.
Unlucky?
Where do I find them?
I think Victory Fountain Park.
You tell me how to get there.
It's on any map, man.
It's North of the city.
You know the Chong District?
You just keep going North.
Did you manage to speak to the embassy?
Yes, I called them myself.
Someone will be here in a few hours.
Thank you.
I also found the newspaper articles.
Oh, yeah?
And I have a question for you.
Go on.
What year is this?
I'm sorry, what?
What year do you think it is?
It's 1985. Why?
- 2018.
- 2018... you mean like 2018, yeah?
- 2018? Why, why not?
Yeah? It makes sense to me.
I mean, if they can w-w-warp space,
they can probably w-w-warp time as well.
That's how they managed to
stay hidden for so long!
Who?
You need to get me out of here, doc.
You need to get me out of here.
- They've got my daughter!
- I'm sorry. I can't do that.
And you're hurting me.
S-sorry, sorry.
I just...
Look, it doesn't matter anyway, does it?
In a few hours I'm not gonna be
your problem anymore.
You lied to me!
What is it you actually do
for nice old Master Trahn?
- Maya...
- I married a hero!
Not a gangster.
Get out!
The thing is he really believes it.
They all do!
Surely my best student knows that.
Of course but...
- Never mind.
- What is it?
What's bothering you?
The photos.
He looks exactly the same.
It's been over 30 years.
Shouldn't he look a lot older?
Maybe it's his father
and the girl his sister.
He took his father's identity
to try and escape the pain.
Anna, it is a classic
case of transference.
You should know that!
What?
I'm almost sorry I called
the British embassy for him.
I could have treated him myself
and written a book.
Oh, you can do better than that.
Aliens are so cliché.
My drunken son in law swears...
he saw a UFO above
the park near Chinatown.
Park? What park?
Oh, I don't know, it's...
Oh, it's the one with a fountain.
Victory Fountain Park.
Translation and subtitles by
PEPPER & LALASPAIN
*** SONG LIVES FOR EVER ***
Are you all right?
How did you...?
I don't know.
I don't know what you think you saw.
But this place...
This place...
What time is it?
D'you have the time?
What?!
I've been here longer!
I've been here longer than that!
Hey, can I call someone for you?
No.
I'm... I'm...
I'm looking for my wife.
Your wife?
Is she here with you?
She's been...
She's been abducted.
Abducted?
What do you mean?
- By whom?
- These people.
These...
What are you looking at?
Do you see that?
Yeah?
See that tree?
- We are walking towards it, right?
- Yeah.
Why aren't we getting any closer?
How... how is that possible?
I don't know.
There's something else I wanna show you.
Let me see your phone.
Just hold it.
What? I don't...
Tilt it up!
What is that?
An optical illusion?
It's this place.
It's all messed up.
There more you interact with it,
the more it messes you up.
There is something really
messed up about that place.
There's someone you need to meet.
I'll drive.
Hey there.
He's with me.
How's our British doing?
He's fine.
The embassy people just showed up.
The British Embassy?
Yeah, two big guys.
Bao took them to the conference room 2.
Thank you so much for coming.
Andrew, look out!
What the...?
I guess they are not from the embassy.
They're not from any
embassy around here.
Who is this guy?
Anna, Anna, come on.
You need to get me out of here, alright?
It's only a matter of time before
those things come back here.
You mean the aliens?
I can't believe I'm saying this!
I should have my head examined.
Look, they're not aliens, alright?
I call them drones.
They're humans that are
controlled by the aliens
through those spider things
in the back of their necks.
Why didn't he die?
You shot him in the head!
Yeah, you shoot him in the head,
you can shoot him in the leg,
shoot him in the arm,
it doesn't really matter, alright?
The only thing you can do is...
to pull those spiders out to
stop the motor functioning.
Where do I find them?
They have my wife.
I don't know. I guess we could
go back to the park, right?
I mean... that's the only clue I've got!
What the hell?
Okay! That's as far as you go!
I'm sorry. You can't come in here.
What's going on here?
This area is restricted.
There was a gas explosion.
- It's not safe.
- Gas explosion?
In the middle of a park?
There were pipes underneath.
- What are you talking about? Let me
have a look... - Hey, stop! Stop!
- Let me have a look! - Stop!
- You can't come! -I'm very sorry!
Sorry, Officer.
We are just about to leave.
Sorry! Sorry!
- What are you talking about
gas explosion? - Let's go!
What's he talking about gas explosion?
More like a meteorite hit.
They're smart fuckers, aren't they?
They knew we'd find one of their entry
points so they've shut it down.
Yeah? Now what do we do?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
My wife's in there!
Yeah, my kid's in there as well
but I don't know, do I?
Let's get out of here.
Six, five...
Four, three...
Two... one.
And you are now asleep
but you can still hear my voice.
Think back to Lucy.
Daddy!
Now, think back to
when she went missing.
I can't!
Yes, you can!
This is your mind!
You control it.
You can remember.
Lucy?
You can do it!
They're not letting me!
You are safe.
You are with me.
I'll keep you safe.
Just relax.
Relax!
Let's use a safe word.
When you hear the word "Lucy..."
You are going to wake up refreshed.
You got it?
Okay.
Let's try again.
I searched.
I didn't sleep for days.
I searched everywhere for her.
She was gone.
It's like she just
vanished into thin air.
The police.
They were no help.
Every time I went to her room...
I don't know,
it was like I was feeling this...
intense nausea.
That happened to me to.
They tried to tell me
it was mental but it wasn't.
There was something physically
wrong with that space.
I'm sure of it.
One day I... I found him.
I finally found someone who believed me.
He was a doctor.
I just can't remember his name.
Relax! Who did you find?
I can't!
I'm talking about other dimensions.
Other planes of existence.
Who did you find?
Who believed you?
He was a doctor!
Fight it, Andrew.
Fight it.
Shut up!
He knows where my wife is.
I need to know!
Who did you find?
Who believed you?
Lucy!
Are you okay?
Gong.
What?
I talked to Gong.
I spoke to him on the phone.
He's the only one who believed me.
He knew all my symptoms.
Everything about Lucy's disappearance
before I even said it.
Dr. Jiao Gong.
Jiao Gong. A Chinese scientist.
He lived around here
in Ho Chi Minh City.
We have to find him.
Dr. Gong!
Never heard of him.
Dr. Gong. My name is Andrew Quinn.
I'm from London.
You remember me?
You have the wrong person.
No, I don't. We've met before.
30 years ago.
But to me it feels like three days.
They have my daughter.
They have my wife.
Please.
Come on.
What most people don't realize
is the whole concept of Feng Shui,
originated from contact between alien
life forms and ancient civilizations.
Please don't touch anything!
Most of these are for tourists,
but there are one or two
pieces that are irreplaceable.
This...
This is what they were after.
This is a "Luo Pan," right?
An ancient Chinese compass?
They're ancient texts claiming that
the traditional Luo Pan compass
was modeled after an alien navigation
device that was so powerful,
it could cross dimensions.
An immortal Luo Pan
that blew apart on
its first journey here.
Journey from where?
Another galaxy?
Another dimension.
It is said that they've been
searching for pieces of this device,
for hundreds of our lifetimes.
To put it back together.
But wasn't the whole ancient
Feng Shui a compass?
Just a misunderstanding
of how magnets work?
Our old compasses are pale replicas
of the extraterrestrial original.
They're barely to measure
fluctuations in "Chi."
They use magnetic needles
at their center.
But the immortal Luo Pan,
had a piece of an ancient
meteorite at its core.
A stone not of this world.
Like the one you're wearing?
Come.
Please, please don't touch anything.
This represents years and years of work.
I've devoted my whole
life to this research.
I've seen this.
This?
You've seen this shape?
Yes, I've seen that.
They had my daughter,
and these other people in cages.
And they were all spaced out
at exact distances
leading towards this.
And they had green jade discs
strapped to their necks.
Here.
I built this machine
to measure and locate disruptions
to the natural flow of Chi,
using ancient Feng Shui principles.
You see, my family have been tracking
the visitors for generations.
They're almost impossible
to find because, as we've learnt,
they can manipulate dimensional flux.
Bend space time.
But in doing so,
they disrupt our
three-dimensional world.
They disrupt the natural flow of Chi.
Oh, they can do more than disrupt it.
The things I've seen...
What?
You're saying you've actually
made contact with them?
Oh, I've had contact
with them, alright, yeah.
Ain't that something?
Now this...
This is what they're looking for.
I want you to take it.
Hold it.
Let your aura infuse
the meteorite fragment.
And then, place it there.
The Guide Stone Filament.
Our long search...
is over.
You led them to me!
Thanks for the drink, Mister Hero.
Not a hero yet.
Just finished basic training.
- You're my everything
- You're my hero.
I married a hero!
Not a gangster.
Hey!
You need to focus.
Focus!
Come on! Wake up!
I'll get his attention.
You get away.
No. Wait.
There's no time.
Hey!
What the hell is going on here?
Where am I?
What am I doing here?
I demand to know what's going on here!
Hey!
Hey, hey!
You're all right, man?
Run!
What?
Fight it!
Come on, man!
I know you're in there!
Oh, come on!
When you hear the word "Lucy..."
You are going to wake up.
Lucy.
You know that wasn't me, right?
I'm glad to have you back.
Sorry about that, man.
Are you good?
Let's go get 'em!
I won the fight, though, right?
No man.
I did.
I think it's this way.
Wait.
I don't recognize this place.
Something is very wrong
with the vibe here.
It's not here. Come on.
Let's go.
Andrew!
Hello?
And...
Anna?
Oh, my God!
What the hell did they do to you?
We need your form to
function in your world.
Our old vessels were wearing thin.
We had used them for too long.
So we got a new one.
You're seeing this too, right?
There's three of them.
Yeah.
What have you done with my daughter?
And my wife?
We need them.
For what?
We need them to get home.
We have been here for too long.
The cycle between our form
gets shorter and shorter.
Soon we will not survive.
Keep them talking.
Cowards!
Why don't you show us your true form?
Our true form?
Your mind would not comprehend.
We exist in eight dimensions,
while you perceive only four.
Let's go.
It would be like an ant,
trying to understand quantum mechanics.
But since you insist,
This isn't good.
Run!
Oh, shit!
You can't go.
You have such strong and beautiful Chi.
And for the next phase,
we need all that we can get.
Lucy?!
Daddy! Daddy!
Help me!
Get me out of here!
Maya!
You're here!
You found me!
Of course I did!
It is time.
What?
Lucy, I'm gonna get you
out of here, okay?
What's happening?
We are opening the door.
What are you doing to them?
We chose them for their strong Chi.
To bring us home.
Lucy!
Will they travel with you?
No, Connor Wu. No.
Your kind cannot cross
the portal and survive.
And you'd disrupt our doorway home.
We cannot have that.
Besides...
there won't be anything
left of them to take along.
No!
You let her go!
Do it!
Lucy!
No!
Stop it!
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I'm sorry!
Hey!
- Quinn!
- Huh?
I got this.
It's gonna be okay.
Oh, baby...
You wanted your hero back?
Well, here I am.
Lucy!
Daddy!
Let me look at you.
Are you okay?
- Yes!
- Yeah?
Did they hurt you?
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
Forgive me, sweetheart.
Oh, my God!
Connor?
Connor!
Maya!
Connor?
Connor, is that you?
Maya! Can you hear me?
Connor, I can hear you.
Where are you?
Help!
Translation and subtitles by
PEPPER & LALASPAIN
*** SONG LIVES FOR EVER ***